[
  { // Exercise 1, English, C++, V1
    "Id": 1,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Description_c++_V1",
    "Hint": "Hint_c++_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 1,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 1,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": true,
    "SubtractSystem": "10, 20, ..._c++_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 10,
    "IdNum": 123,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c++_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c++_V1",
    "Feedback": "Feedback_c++_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 0,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cpp_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c++_V1",
    "FilesSize": 2000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, German, C++, V1
    "Id": 2,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_c++_V1",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_c++_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 2,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 1,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": true,
    "SubtractSystem": "10, 20, ..._c++_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 10,
    "IdNum": 123,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c++_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c++_V1",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_c++_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 0,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cpp_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c++_V1",
    "FilesSize": 2000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, English, C#, V1
    "Id": 3,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Description_c#_V1",
    "Hint": "Hint_c#_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 1,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 2,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._c#_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 321,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c#_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c#_V1",
    "Feedback": "Feedback_c#_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 2,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cs_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c#_V1",
    "FilesSize": 4000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, German, C#, V1
    "Id": 4,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 2,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_c#_V1",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_c#_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 2,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 2,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._c#_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 321,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c#_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c#_V1",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_c#_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 2,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cs_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c#_V1",
    "FilesSize": 4000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, English, C++, V2
    "Id": 5,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Description_c++_V2",
    "Hint": "Hint_c++_V2",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 3,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 3,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": true,
    "SubtractSystem": "10, 20, ..._c++_V2",
    "ObtainablePoints": 10,
    "IdNum": 123,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c++_V2",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c++_V2",
    "Feedback": "Feedback_c++_V2",
    "AllowFiles": 0,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cpp_V2",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c++_V2",
    "FilesSize": 2000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, German, C++, V2
    "Id": 6,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_c++_V2",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_c++_V2",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 4,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 3,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": true,
    "SubtractSystem": "10, 20, ..._c++_V2",
    "ObtainablePoints": 10,
    "IdNum": 123,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c++_V2",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c++_V2",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_c++_V2",
    "AllowFiles": 0,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cpp_V2",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c++_V2",
    "FilesSize": 2000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, English, C#, V2
    "Id": 7,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Description_c#_V2",
    "Hint": "Hint_c#_V2",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 3,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 4,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._c#_V2",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 321,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c#_V2",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c#_V2",
    "Feedback": "Feedback_c#_V2",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 2,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cs_V2",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c#_V2",
    "FilesSize": 4000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, German, C#, V2
    "Id": 8,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 2,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_c#_V2",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_c#_V2",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 4,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 4,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._c#_V2",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 321,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c#_V2",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c#_V2",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_c#_V2",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 2,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cs_V2",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c#_V2",
    "FilesSize": 4000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, English, C++, V3
    "Id": 9,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Description_c++_V3",
    "Hint": "Hint_c++_V3",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 5,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 5,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": true,
    "SubtractSystem": "10, 20, ..._c++_V3",
    "ObtainablePoints": 10,
    "IdNum": 123,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c++_V3",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c++_V3",
    "Feedback": "Feedback_c++_V3",
    "AllowFiles": 0,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cpp_V3",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c++_V3",
    "FilesSize": 2000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, German, C++, V3
    "Id": 10,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_c++_V3",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_c++_V3",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 6,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 5,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": true,
    "SubtractSystem": "10, 20, ..._c++_V3",
    "ObtainablePoints": 10,
    "IdNum": 123,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c++_V3",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c++_V3",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_c++_V3",
    "AllowFiles": 0,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cpp_V3",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c++_V3",
    "FilesSize": 2000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, English, C#, V3
    "Id": 11,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 1,
    "Description": "Description_c#_V3",
    "Hint": "Hint_c#_V3",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 5,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 6,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._c#_V3",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 321,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c#_V3",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c#_V3",
    "Feedback": "Feedback_c#_V3",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 2,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cs_V3",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c#_V3",
    "FilesSize": 4000
  },
  { // Exercise 1, German, C#, V3
    "Id": 12,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 2,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_c#_V3",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_c#_V3",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 6,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 6,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._c#_V3",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 321,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c#_V3",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c#_V3",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_c#_V3",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 2,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.cs_V3",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c#_V3",
    "FilesSize": 4000
  },
  { // Exercise 2, English, Python, V1
    "Id": 13,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 6,
    "Description": "Description_py_V1",
    "Hint": "Hint_py_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 7,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 7,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": true,
    "SubtractSystem": "10, 20, ..._py_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 10,
    "IdNum": 234,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_py_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_py_V1",
    "Feedback": "Feedback_py_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 0,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.py_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_py_V1",
    "FilesSize": 2500
  },
  { // Exercise 2, German, Python, V1
    "Id": 14,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 6,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_py_V1",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_py_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 8,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 7,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": true,
    "SubtractSystem": "10, 20, ..._py_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 10,
    "IdNum": 234,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_py_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_py_V1",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_py_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 0,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.py_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_py_V1",
    "FilesSize": 2500
  },
  { // Exercise 2, English, Java, V1
    "Id": 15,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 3,
    "Description": "Description_java_V1",
    "Hint": "Hint_java_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 7,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 8,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._java_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 432,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_java_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_java_V1",
    "Feedback": "Feedback_java_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 1,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.java_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_java_V1",
    "FilesSize": 5000
  },
  { // Exercise 2, German, Java, V1
    "Id": 16,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 3,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_java_V1",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_java_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 8,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 8,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._java_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 432,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_java_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_java_V1",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_java_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 1,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.java_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_java_V1",
    "FilesSize": 5000
  },
  { // Exercise 3, German, C, V1
    "Id": 17,
    "FkProgrammingLanguageId": 5,
    "Description": "Beschreibung_c_V1",
    "Hint": "Hinweis_c_V1",
    "FkExerciseLanguageId": 9,
    "FkTestSuiteId": 9,
    "FieldLines": 18,
    "GradingFlag": false,
    "SubtractSystem": "n_10, 20, ..._c_V1",
    "ObtainablePoints": 5,
    "IdNum": 543,
    "Solution": "n_Solution_c_V1",
    "Prefill": "n_Prefill_c_V1",
    "Feedback": "Rückmeldung_c_V1",
    "AllowFiles": 4,
    "FilesRequired": 0,
    "FilesRegex": "n_*.c_V1",
    "FilesDescription": "n_FilesDescription_c_V1",
    "FilesSize": 100
  }
]